https://coastalrugs.com/terms-and-conditions

All Inventory Specials / Closeouts
User Account (optional)
Username:
Password:
Remember me
Login
Forgot Password?
Get an Account
Mailing List
Subscribe
Already a member?Manage your preferences.
News & Announcements
Our store is currently not accepting new orders.
We'll are rebuilding our catalog with a whole new lineup of exciting products.  Please contact us directly with any questions or inquiries.
Home
Terms and Conditions
Terms & Conditions
CoastalRugs.com - Terms and Conditions ("Terms")
Last updated: Oct 01, 2017
Please read these Terms and Conditions ("Terms", "Terms and Conditions") carefully before using the http://CoastalRugs.com website operated by "Coastal Designer Rugs, LLC" ("us", "we", or "our").
Your access to and use of the Service is conditioned on your acceptance of and compliance with these Terms. These Terms apply to all visitors, users, and others who access or use the Service.
By accessing or using the Service you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you disagree with any part of the terms then you may not access the Service.
Purchases
If you wish to purchase any product or service made available through the Service ("Purchase"), you may be asked to supply certain information relevant to your Purchase including, without limitation, Personally Identifiable Information (PII).
See our 'Privacy Policy' regarding Personally Identifiable Information
See our 'Return Policy' regarding Purchases
Subscriptions
Some parts of the Service may be billed on a subscription basis ("Subscription(s)"). You will be billed in advance for future delivery of goods/services.  This is treated the same as a general Purchase, and follows the same guidelines.  Subscriptions are handled on a fixed schedule.  For instance, monthly subscriptions are 'batched' and processed a few days before the end of the month.  Then any shipments made to all subscribers in the following few days.  It is possible to subscribe after the batch date for the month but before the end of the calendar month.  Any perceived delay is adjusted for at the close of the subscription period, as the dates work out for an expedited last cycle.
See our Return Policy
Content
Our Service may allow you to post, link, store, share and otherwise make available certain information, text, graphics, videos, or other material ("Content").  You are responsible for the lawfulness of that information being shared we us, and the general public.  All information provided in the context of 'Comments', 'Reviews', or similar open/common forums (outside private communication and the checkout process), may be used by us in any form, and at any time (i.e. marketing campaigns, testimonials, etc).  This Content becomes our property.  We reserve the right to remove/redact/edit any Content.
See our Privacy Policy
Affiliates
If applicable to your user account, any affiliate commission accrued is calculated at the end of each month, and paid by the 10th of the next month (or the next available business day), via the method chosen at the time of registration.  Registration requires approval.  All information requested during affiliate signup subject to the same privacy terms as other personal data.  Application does not mean assured approval, and approval is up to the sole discretion of us.  A tracking code is accessible in your account page to create custom links and such to our website.  Commission rate subject to change at anytime.  Participation in this program is completely voluntary.  We shall not be responsible for any costs/liability for its use by its participants.
See our Privacy Policy
Links To Other Web Sites
Our Service may contain links to third-party web sites or services that are not owned or controlled by us.
We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for: the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party web sites or services. You further acknowledge and agree that we shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on or through any such web sites or services.
See our Privacy Policy
Limit of Liability
Any judgment or loss by a user of our Site/Service shall be limited to the value of the particular transaction that caused the loss.  That is to say, that any judgment/penalty shall be limited to value of the purchased item or the service's cycle-value, whichever is lower.  User waives all rights to punitive damages, and will hold Coastal Designer Rugs, LLC and its agents blameless for any liability beyond that already noted.  At no time, and under no circumstances shall we be liable for anything beyond that value, including, but not limited to: travel, shipping costs, legal fees, incidental damage, medical expenses, punitive damages.  The Uniform Commercial Code of Connecticut shall be considered on points not covered, and any arbitration handled in the state of Connecticut.
Changes
We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time. If a revision is material, we will post said change on this page at least 30 days' notice prior to any new terms taking effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at our sole discretion.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us via our Contact Us page.
See our Contact Us page
